var questions = [{
	"question": "4 x 7 = ... ",
	"option1": "24",
	"option2": "28",
	"option3": "14",
	"option4": "32",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "3 x 9 = ... ",
	"option1": "21",
	"option2": "12",
	"option3": "27",
	"option4": "18",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "5 x 6 = ...",
	"option1": "30",
	"option2": "35",
	"option3": "40",
	"option4": "45",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "6 x 7 = ... ",
	"option1": "32",
	"option2": "36",
	"option3": "40",
	"option4": "42",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "9 x 8 = ... ",
	"option1": "17",
	"option2": "64",
	"option3": "72",
	"option4": "81",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "3 x 2 x 6 = ...",
	"option1": "24",
	"option2": "36",
	"option3": "42",
	"option4": "48",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "2 x 4 x 7 = ...",
	"option1": "40",
	"option2": "42",
	"option3": "56",
	"option4": "60",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "2 x 5 x 8 = ... ",
	"option1": "40",
	"option2": "60",
	"option3": "70",
	"option4": "80",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "2 x 2 x 9 = ... ",
	"option1": "36",
	"option2": "40",
	"option3": "45",
	"option4": "46",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "5 x 2 x 7 = ... ",
	"option1": "27",
	"option2": "70",
	"option3": "72",
	"option4": "77",
	"answer": "2"
}];